大家好，漂亮的人们，祝贺你们顺利通过了这门课程。
Hello you beautiful people and congratulations for making it through the course.
所以我们一起的旅程让你从学习如何打开航站楼和运行命令开始
So our journey together has taken you right from learning how to open the terminal and run commands
一直到创建文件归档、编写自动化脚本和管理数以千计的
all the way to creating file archives writing automated scripts and managing thousands of pieces of
使用包管理器的软件。
software using the package manager.
所以你们真的走了一段令人难以置信的漫长道路，我为你们感到难以置信的骄傲。
So you truly have come an incredibly long way and I'm incredibly proud of you.
9~10成熟。
Well done.
我只想拍这段视频，非常感谢你们陪我走这趟旅程
And I just wanted to shoot this video to say thank you very much for coming along with me on this journey
通过Linux命令行，我希望您从我们的共同旅程中获益良多
through that Linux command line and I hope that you've received some benefit from our journey together
我祝你在未来一帆风顺。
and I wish you the very best in the future.
如果你真的想学到更多，一定要看一下我的其他课程，并密切关注
And if you do want to learn more do take a look at some of my other courses and keep an eye out for
有关更高级课程的信息，使您的学习更上一层楼。
information about more advanced courses to take your learning to the next level.
事实上，我会在资源部分为您提供特别折扣优惠券链接
And in fact I'll be putting special discount coupon links for you in the resources section for this
录像带或者这附近的某个地方。
video or somewhere around here.
对于我所有的课程，只是为了感谢你成为一名学生，所以，去吧，报名参加你想要的任何课程吧
For all my courses just to say thank you for being a student so go ahead and enroll in whatever you'd
喜欢。
like.
如果你有什么特别想学的，或者你想学的另一门课程
And if there's something in particular that you would like to learn or another course that you would
喜欢我去创造。
like me to create.
我总是听取建议，所以给我发个信息，我会尽我所能去实现它。
I always listen to suggestions so send me a message and I'll do what ever I can to make that happen.
如果你百分之百修完了这门课。
And if you finish the course 100 percent.
你应该很快就会收到你给我的电子邮件的结业证书，让你打印出来，然后
You should soon receive a certificate of completion from you to me by email for you to print off and
放上你的链接个人资料，或者自豪地向世界展示你现在是Linux的大师。
put on your linked in profile or to show proudly to the world that you are now and Linux master.
如果您在通过认证时遇到任何问题，请与我的支持团队联系
And if you do have any troubles getting the certificate through do contact you to me support team on
支持你到我的网站，他们会帮你解决的。
support at you to me dot com and they'll sort it all out for you.
除此之外，我祝你万事如意，并希望你能得到我最大的敬意和感激
And other than that I wish you the absolute best and hope you have my utmost respect and gratitude for
试着投资于你的学习。
trying to invest in your learning.
祝你一切顺利，希望不久能再次见到你。
So good luck with everything and I hope to have the pleasure of meeting you again soon.